If you refuse to put chocolate chips in
your Ninja Creamy recipes because they
somehow turn out flavorless, chalky, and
low-key taste like a crayon, I have the
solution for you. This chocolate chip
hack has to be the greatest invention of
all time. Look at all those chocolate
chips in there. Oh my god. But before we
get into the hack, let's prep a vanilla
base so we can turn this into a
stratella protein ice. Literally just
five ingredients, which I'll have in the
description down below, but I'll go
through them real quick. High protein
milk, sweetener, salt, zantham gum,
vanilla bean paste. Then you can just
blend that all together. Throw it in the
freezer for at least 16 hours. Take it
out, run under hot water for about a
minute, and then throw it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. Now,
let's get into the hat. So, while your
creamy is running, you're going to grab
15 to 20 g of chocolate chips with 2 to
3 g of coconut oil. The ratio is
approximately 7 to 1, and you're going
to melt that in the microwave in 30
secondond increments until it comes
melted like this. And then you're just
going to use that as a mixing. And you
have to work pretty quickly with this
because it will melt the ice cream. It
is pretty hot. Essentially, what's
happening on the inside is it's
hardening while it's spinning, which
creates these little flakes or pockets
of chocolate, which is exactly how
Stretchella ice cream is made. If these
aren't the best chocolate chips you've
had in the Ninja Creamy, I will
personally pay you my follower amount in
dollars.